

SWANN MARTIN

CONTACT INFO

- Brussels
- +32 456 59 60 82
- M swannmartin1988@gmail.com
- Portfolio: <u>swannmartin.xyz</u>
- @swann.martin
- https://github.com/swann-martin
- Driving Licence & car
- # Fluent in English, French Native

PROFILE

Web and mobile developer specialised in React and React Native with TypeScript. I worked on several apps for construction industry sector, aerospace, small companies and city councils. I have strong adaptation skills and I am organised. In the past, have worked for years in an English speaking context and lived for 2 years in England.

PROJETS https://github.com/swann-martin

Burger Shop: React, TypeScript, Supabase

Mariage: Nextjs, Tailwind

Sauvons la friche Josaphat: Wordpress

L'anerie: Deno, Fresh, Typescript, Tailwind

Portfolio: React, TypeScript, Scss

My Sofas: React, tailwind

Sharewash: React Native, Zustand, Firebase

WashatHome: React, Redux, axios, Leaflet,

postgres, scss, node

Jummp a CV Generator: Symfony, PHP, twig,

iQuery, CSS

HOBBIES



Climbing sports





Decentralization



GNU/Linux,



Open Source



House Renovation

REACT DEVELOPER

SKILLS



Github

Organised, Rigourous, Flexible, Reactive, Curious Can do attitude, Decisive

Wordpress

Fiama

EXPERIENCE



FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Freelance Developer | February 2023

Git

Freelance developer, specialized in React, React Native with Typescript. See my profile on Malt.be



[</>] DEVELOPER

Beecoming | December 2021 - November 2022

As a developper there, I was in charge of implementing new features, fixing bugs, and turning designs into code in Angular and React.

- I worked on an app for guided tours in React Native, tablets actions were sent through websockets, the APi was in Nestjs and front-end panel admin in React.
- Application in Angular, Ionic, SCSS, Material UI, backend API Node, Websockets, FS, Express.
- Langages : TypeScript/JavaScript, Php, .Net
- Tools: Agile, Scrum, Git, Jira, Office 360, ios, android



SALES REPRESENTATIVE LANGUAGE COURSE Oxford Intensive School of English | 2014 - 2020

- Managing a booking office for a high end language courses brand in Bordeaux & Lille

FORMATION

O'CLOCK: Training React | 06/21 - 08/21

Training in React.js, Redux.

End of training project: Technologies: React, Redux, Node, postgreSql

WEBFORCE 3: Training Dev | 01/21 -04/21

Certifications professionnelles CNCP (catégorie C):

- Techniques d'intégration Web (front-end) : (HTML / CSS, JavaScript / jQuery, Angular, CMS: Wordpress)
- <u>Techniques de développement Web (back-end) :</u> (MySQL, PHP, Symfony).

End of training project: CV generator website. Technologies: Symfony/Twig/SQL/CSS

UNIVERSITY OF PORTSMOUTH / PARIS X

Master2 FLE / PGCE MFL | Sept 2011 - Juin 2013

- Double diploma Master 2 Teaching Modern Foreign Languages | FLE LYCÉE MIREILLE GRENET COMPIEGNE **BACCALAUREAT Sciences Engineering technologies**

spe Electronics with Honors | 2007